Wieslaw Z. Wisniewski Papers, 1939-1994 (bulk 1976-1990)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 2: Research Files, 1939-1994
  - Subseries 3: Asteroids, 1974-1994
    - 1153 Wallenbergia, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 1221 Amor, 1988, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 1235 Schorria, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - 1270 Datura, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 1322 Copernicus, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - 1374 Isora, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - 1376 Michelle, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 1382 Gerti, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 1419 Danzig, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 1453 Fennia, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - 1468 Zomba, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - 1504 Lappeenranta, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - 1572 Posnania, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - 1580 Betulia, April, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - 1580 Betulia, May, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Betulia CTIO, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - 1580 Betulia Observing Report, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - 1583 Antilochus, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - 1593 Fagnes, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - 1613 Smiley, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - 1620 Geographos, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - 1621 Druzhba, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - 1640 Nemo, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - 1656 Suomi, 1986, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - 1657 Roemera, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - 1653 Innes, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - 1667 Pels, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - 1675 Simonida, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - 1777 Gehrels, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - 1865 Cerberus, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - 1906 Neaf, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - 1917 Cuyo and CCD, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - 1943 Anteros, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - 1951 Lick, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - 1980 Tezcatlipoca, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - 1981 Midas, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - 1991 Darwin (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - 2017 Wesson, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - 2035 Stearns, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - 2064 Thomsen, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - 2212 Hephaistos, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 2253 Espinette, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 2256 Wisniewski, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 2049 Grietje, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 2059 Baboquivari, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 2289 McMillan, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 2382 Nonie, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 2449 Kenos, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 1977 CB = 2491 Tvashtri, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 2501 Lohja, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 2577 Litva, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 2642 Vesala, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 2659 Millis, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - 2714 Matti, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - 2794 Kulik, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 2886 Tinkaping, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - 2954 Delsenme, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - 3066 McFadden, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - 3101 Goldberger, 1987, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - 3103 1982 BB-I, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - 3103 1982 BB-II, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - 3116 Goodricke, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - 3122 Florence, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - 3149 Okudjeva, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - 3169 Ostro (1981 LA), 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - 3199 Nefertiti (1982 RA), Radar Target, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - 3200 Phaethon, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - 3253 Gradia, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - 3255 Tholen, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - 3268 De Sanctis 90", 1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - 3287 Olmstead, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - 3309 Brorfelde, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - 3317 1984 KF, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - 3350 Scobee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - 3361 Orpheus (1982 HR), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - 3362 Khufu, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - 3507 Vilas, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - 3554 Amun, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - 3577 Putilin, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - 3581 Alvarez, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - 3594 Scotti, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - 3628 Boznemcova, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - 3638 Davis, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - 3691 Bede, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - 3753 Cruithne, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - 3824 Brenda Lee, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - 3908, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - 3908 1980 PA, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - 4179 Toutatis, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 4179 Toutatis, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - 4197 Morpheus, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - 4272 Entsuji, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - 1983 AG/4435 Holt, 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - 1986 RC2 4483, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - 4503 Cleobulus, 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - 1988 NF 4558 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 1990 SQ/4954 ERIC, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 1990 DA = 5332 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - (5693) 1993 EA (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - (5751) 1992 AC (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - (5836) 1993 MF (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 1981 ED35, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 1981 ET42, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 1983 RD Radar Target, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 1983 PA, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 1985 RV, 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 1986 DA (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 1986 JK (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 1986 RA (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 1987 SL (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 1988 WC (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - 1989 DA, 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - 1989 JA, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - 1989 UP (SS-1), 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - 1989 VA (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - 1989 VB (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - 1990 HA (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - 1990 KA, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - 1990 SA (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - 1990 SS, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - 1990 TR (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - 1990 UA (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - 1990 UP (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - 1991 AQ (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - 1991 EE (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - 1991 EE (SS-48), 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - 1991 VA (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - 1991 KD, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - 1992 LR (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Long-term Ephemeris of Various Asteroids, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - A-A-A Asteroids, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - E Asteroids, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Asteroid CCD Test, 1975-1985 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Photometry Transformation UBVRI, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Transformation, 1987-1993 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - UBV Transformation, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Transformations 90", 1986 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Transformation Observations, April, 1986-September, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Extinction, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Log 90", 1990 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - 8 Color Photometer (Tholen files), 1978, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Anonymous Asteroid, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Asteroid Observations by Wisniewski, Anderson, and Zellner, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Aspect Data for the Asteroids, 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Subseries 4: Proposals and Grants, 1977-1994
    - Stuart Mufson reports, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - KR Aurigae papers on X-Rays, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Photometric Standards for Comet Photometry, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Comet Churyumov-Gerasimenko, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Proposal to Space Telescope Science Institute, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Solar Objects proposals, 1982-1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Acquisition of TI 800X800 Three Phase CCD Chips, 1985-1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Precision Photometry of the Nuclear Region of Comets, Evaluation, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Colors and Shapes of Galileo Targets 243 Ida and 951 Gaspra, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Physical Studies of Small Asteroids and Cometary Cores, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Calibration of GaAs Photomultiplier Tubes for Standardization of the SSP Detector, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 5: Miscellaneous Research, 1975-1994
    - Satellites, dark asteroids, and comet observations, 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Radio sources, 1982-1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - University of Arizona observatories, Telescope Time proposals, 1984-1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Radar targets, 1984-1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Observing notes, 1986-1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - SUN, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Image Reduction and Analysis facility and SUNOS, 1988-1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Series 3: Scholarly Files, 1975-1993
  Includes publications written by Dr. Wisniewski, book reviews by Wisniewski, and meetings.
  - Subseries 1: Publications, 1975-1993
    Arranged alphabetically and is a partial record of Dr. Wisniewski writing career.
    - 1011 plus 496 and 1217 plus 348: Two New Candidate BL Lacertae Objects, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - 1367 Nongoma PHO Lag Period, 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - 0.35—35 Micron Photometry of Polarized QSOs, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - The Complete Light Curve of 1992, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Ground Based Photometry of Asteroid 951, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Highly Variable Objects in the Solar System, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Minor Planets and Related Objects. XVIII: UBV photometry and surface composition, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - On Interstellar Reddening Law in the Taurus Dark Clouds, 1978-1981, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Photometric Observations of the Bright Nuclei of Five X-Ray Globular Clusters, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Physical Studies of Small Asteroids, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - P/Tempel 2 CCD and Photometry article, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - P/Tempel 2 final paper (Icarus), 1989 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - P/Tempel 2 Observations, May, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - QSO Polarization, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Reflectivity Curve and Photometry of Eros, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Spectrophotometry and Ubvri Photometry of Eros, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Strongly Variable Objects in the Solar System, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - A Technique for Measuring the Light Curves of Cometary Nuclei, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - The Unusual Light Curve of 1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 2: Book Reviews, 1986-1993
    - Light Curves, 1986-1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Small Main-belt Asteroid Light Curvey survey, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 3: Conferences and Meetings, 1988-1993
    - Asteroids II Conference, Tucson, Arizona, March 8, 1988-March 11, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Pluto Meeting, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)